hijinksensue.com 2011-11-09

# HijiNKS ENSUE – A Geek Webcomic - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to HijiNKS ENSUE. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that HijiNKS ENSUE collects, and the ways in which HijiNKS ENSUE uses that personal information.

**This privacy statement**

This [privacy statement](http://www.freenetlaw.com/free-privacy-statement.php) is based on a [Freenetlaw](http://www.freenetlaw.com/) template supplied by [Employment Law Contracts](http://www.employmentlawcontracts.co.uk/).

**Personal information collection**

HijiNKS ENSUE may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * [information about your use of this website]
  * [information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website]
  * [information about transactions carried out over this website]
  * [information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and]
  * [any other information that you send to HijiNKS ENSUE.]

**Using personal information**

HijiNKS ENSUE may use your personal information to:

  * [administer this website;]
  * [personalize the website for you;]
  * [enable your access to and use of the website services;]
  * [publish information about you on the website;]
  * [send to you products that you purchase;]
  * [supply to you services that you purchase;]
  * [send you statements and invoices;]
  * [collect payments from you; and]
  * [send you marketing communications.]

Where HijiNKS ENSUE discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, HijiNKS ENSUE may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**

HijiNKS ENSUE will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

HijiNKS ENSUE will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.]

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that HijiNKS ENSUE collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which HijiNKS ENSUE operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.]

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**

HijiNKS ENSUE may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

HijiNKS ENSUE is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Contact HijiNKS ENSUE**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or HijiNKS ENSUE’s treatment of your personal information, please write to:

  * by email to comics [at] hijinksensue [dot] com; or
  * by post to:

HijiNKS ENSUE  
PO Box 1507  
Little Elm, TX  
75068
